thenewsteller.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy – The News Teller

**THENEWSTELLER PRIVACY POLICY**  
Privacy of our visitor is what matters most. To ensure the privacy of users, our company designed the policy. We anticipate our users will go through our terms and conditions. This very privacy statement propagate the working methodology of our company.  
We also entertain removal request [removal request form](https://www.thenewsteller.com/removal-request/). Please Mention news post and your claim in the form. 

**Privacy:**  
We recognize that privacy of your personal information is vital. Her is information on what sort of personal data we receive, when you visit this website and how we safeguard your information and what measures we take to shield your privacy.

**Log Files:**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP(internet protocol)address, your ISP(internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw), the browser you used to visit our site(i.e. Firefox or Google Chrome),the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
We do use cookies that are stored by some websites on your computer directory when you visit them, like your personal preferences when you visit our site. This enables us to store information about you. Same cookies system is performed by other search engines and third parties services or partners on our site to identify visitors. But that can’t be performed without your permission as most of the browser allow you to set security settings by showing you popup once in your visit or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.  
**Usage Tracking:**  
We track users traffic patterns in our site but fulfill the privacy rules and regulations and neither sell nor transfer the personal identifiable information to outside parties. However, personal information is just disclosed to those trusted third parties who help us in operating our website and business and indirectly serves you via our website. Moreover, we also ensured the confidentiality of visitors personal information from our trusted third parties. Disclosure of non-personal information regarding interest and choice of visitor, etc. for advertising and marketing purpose is permitted by law and same is also provided by us for survey purpose.

**Online Privacy Policy**

We set our online privacy policy for those users who collected information via our website and we have no concern with those users who collected information offline.

**Your Consent**

You consent our terms and conditions by using our website. In case of any change in policy in future, rules will stand modified and applied accordingly.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Any modification in online privacy policy will be appeared on this page. This online privacy policy was modified on 3 February 2015.

**Contacting Us**

We always believes on quality and improvement. That’s why, any query about online privacy policy will be entertained. Feel free to submit your query by [contact form](https://www.thenewsteller.com/contact-us/).
